<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Assignments on Modern Research Methods: Cumulative Science, Big Data, and Meta-Analysis</title>
    <link>/assignment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Assignments on Modern Research Methods: Cumulative Science, Big Data, and Meta-Analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/assignment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Final project</title>
      <link>/assignment/final-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/assignment/final-project/</guid>
      <description>For your final project, you will perform some (hypothetical) economic analyses and use your newfound vocabulary and skills to make a recommendation.
You will submit two files on Learning Suite:
A PDF of of a 2–3-page memo An Excel file with your technical appendix  You will be graded based on the rubric posted linked below. Though there are correct answers for the different market equilibria and the differential effects of taxes across states and firms, there is no one correct recommendation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Problem set 1</title>
      <link>/assignment/01-problem-set/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/assignment/01-problem-set/</guid>
      <description>Submit this as a PDF on Learning Suite. Show your work when possible.
1 Download one of these datasetsSource: Global Consumption and Income Project. All incomes expressed in 2005 USD PPP.
 (they’re identical; one is an Excel file, one is a CSV file, which is easier to work with in R):
  gcip_raw.xlsx  gcip_raw.csv  Choose five countries you are interested in. For each of these countries, calculate the 90/10 ratio for 1980, 1990, 2000, and 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>